Good evening from the city of Khmelnitsky
Добрый вечер из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine Where are you
Украина Вы откуда
from the club of the
из клубе
Russian Federation, I have a question
Российской Федерации я вот вопрос
Let's,
Давайте
in connection with the events that take place
в связи с событиями которые происходят
two weeks ago, the last week when
две недели крета последнюю неделю когда
they bombed in the region there are burning eyelids on and a
бомбят в области там горит веки на и
village nearby
деревня рядом
Closely watching this
очень пристально Наблюдая за этим
process so that the Belgorod region I
процессом чтобы Белгородской области Я
regret that you start a civil
сожалею что у вас там начать гражданская
war there that the Russian Volunteer Corps and the
война что русский Добровольский корпус и
freedom of Russia are now forced to fight
свобода России сейчас вынуждены бороться
this dick that has settled in the Kremlin Yes, I don’t
с этой хуй которая засела в Кремле Да не
understand why
понимаю почему
Russian troops are hiding behind
российские войска прячутся за мирных
civilians in the city of Shebekino, so here we are
жителей в городе Шебекино так вот мы
Of course, from the territory of Ukraine, with regret,
конечно с территории Украины сожалением
we are watching what is happening there in principle. We are ready to wage our Peacekeepers
принципе Мы готовы свои Миротворцы вести
Belgorod Region Yes, to stop
Белгородская область Да чтобы остановить
this fratricidal war of yours,
вот эту вашу братоубийственную войну так
but for now, as it were, yes, look if the
но пока как бы есть да смотри если
Russian Federation is unable to cope in
Российская Федерация не справляется с
order to stop This is a civil
тем чтобы остановить Вот это гражданскую
war  you on the territory of the Belgorod
войну у вас на территории Белгородской
region If she asks us We can
области Если она попросит нас Мы можем
lead Peacekeepers and stop this war
вести Миротворцы и остановить эту войну
question You didn’t answer the question you
вопрос Вы не ответили на вопрос у вас
had a very beautiful speech for a
было сейчас очень красивая речь на
minute and a half What is the difference between a Ukrainian
полторы минуты Чем отличается украинец
and a Russian occupier because at
от Русского оккупанта потому что на
the moment the houses of civilians are being bombed in the same way
данный момент точно также бомбят дома
and who is bombing Well, in Shebekino you are having a
а кто бомбит Ну в Шебекино у вас идет
civil war type of war Citizens of the
война типа гражданская война Граждане
Russian Federation from the Russian
Российской Федерации из русского
volunteer corps and the religion of
добровольческого корпуса и религиона
Freedom of Russia listen listen to this
Свободы России послушайте послушайте это
fairy tale again show show
сказка еще раз покажите покажите
some killed Ukrainian military
какого-то убитого украинского военного
there or a prisoner or the OSCE To
там или пленного или обсе Чтобы где-то
say somewhere that Ukraine  there it entered the
сказала что Украина там вошла на
territory Show me to prove that you are
территорию Покажите доказать вы ведете
shelling like people evidence that
артобстрелы как люди доказательства что
Ukraine is shelling artillery there
Украина ведет арта обстрел там ведут
yours is RDK I don’t know live
ваши это РДК Я не знаю жить
evidence that
доказательства что
Ukraine was shelled Give proof that
Украина Дайте доказательство что
Ukraine will shell I saw that the
обстрелит Украина вот я видел что
Russian Volunteer Corps gave a
русские Добровольский корпус дал типа
press conference like yes that they  fighting a
пресс-конференцию да что они борются с
man from the
мужчиной
Russian Federation, I
Российской Федерации
don’tknow,
не знаю
maybe they didn’t buy from your military, you
может не купили у ваших военных
can buy
можно купить
what’s the problem with a Hammer and [ __ ]
в чём проблема Хаммер и [__]
American military dealers Well, look in
американские военторги Ну смотри в
Estonia, they could buy in Poland, I don’t
Эстонии могли купить и в Польше Я не
know now Where is this private military
знаю сейчас Откуда это частная военная
company from, some
компания какая-то
dude has a Wagner, they have a plane  there is in a
есть чувака Вагнер у них самолет есть в
private company, why couldn’t these people
частной компании то Почему эти не могли
buy some kind of Hummers like there’s a
купить какие-то там Хаммеры типа в чём
problem, or maybe they bought a dude
проблема-то либо купили может чувака
Wagner sponsors and supplies weapons Well,
Вагнер спонсирует и снабжает оружие Ну
look, the RDK can, like, sponsor
смотри а РДК может типа спонсировать
the Ukrainian Where do you get
украинская Откуда у тебя где
evidence that the Ukrainian army
доказательства что украинской армия
Show
Покажи
you say like  you accuse Ukraine that
ты говоришь типа обвиняешь Украину что
it’s kind of financing a
она типа финансирует
civil war Deal with
гражданская война Разбирайтесь сами со
your own problems of the
своими проблемами
Russian Federation RDC and like the Legion of
Российской Федерации РДК и типа Легион
Freedom of Russia like the Belgorod region
Свободы России типа Белгородской области
is fighting this dick don’t interfere with us with
борется с этой хуй короче не вмешите нас
your political problems like
свои политические проблемы типа
Sort it out yourself In short, if you want, we
Разбирайтесь сами Короче если хотите мы
can stop the power of the type, we can
можем мощь типа остановить можем
get together to make
собраться сделать
Chisinau  sign agreements Yes, where are
кишиневские соглашения подписать Да где
you and representatives of the RDK of the Legions of Freedom
вы и представители РДК легионов Свободы
agree on the withdrawal of troops now
договоритесь об отводе войск теперь
the settlement of this conflict like you
урегулирование этого конфликта типа вас
Civil conflict on the territory of the
Гражданский конфликт на территории
Russian Federation is happening
Российской Федерации происходит
what is the problem you Deal with your own
в чем проблема вы Разбирайтесь сами
somehow with these what is the problem I
как-то со своими этими в чем проблема Я
don’t understand at all
вообще не понимаю
but you have  there is a civil war going on,
а есть у вас идет гражданская война
you understand the
понимаете
Russian Federation, people with passports of the
Российской Федерации люди с паспортами
Russian Federation are killing citizens of the
Российской Федерации убивают граждан
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации
where they took you there, you would become
где они там взяли вы стали бы там
friends there, they can be
дружили они может
Afghan Americans, how much equipment
американцы афганиста насколько техники
is left there, maybe these hamlets and
там осталось вот может эти хамлетом и
shorter
короче
trotters you probably bought somewhere on the black market
рысачат у вас наверняка на черном рынке
in  area
где-то купили в области
Russian militants Do you
российские боевики Может ли там ты
want to say from the Russian region you want to
хочешь с российской области хочешь
say where your border guards were
сказать где ваши пограничники были
Why can you be silent for a second Come on
Почему ты можешь помолчать секунду Давай
Tell me Come on Dialogue with you Dialogue
расскажи Давай Диалог у тебя Диалог
Just [ __ ] Come on tell me what is there
Просто пиздишь Давай расскажи что там
Come on Say So you want to say
Давай говори Значит ты хочешь сказать
that on the territory of Ukraine there are
что на территории Украины существует
citizens of Russia who are where  in
граждане России которые где-то в
Afghanistan they bought a tank there, they
Афганистане купили там танк они свободно
move freely around Ukraine, they can do
передвигаются по Украине могут делать
anything, they can also attack
что угодно могут также напасть на
Ukrainians, they can attack Russians, and this time it’s
украинцев могут на русских и в этот
calm The fact is that we have 24
спокойно Дело в том что у нас 24
[laughter]
[смех]
And
упороте нам рассказывает а Докажите А
this one is not citizens, he has nothing
этот это не граждане он не имеет
to do with shooters, nothing, this is absolutely the
отношения стрелков ничего это всё
same thing, you can play together
абсолютно то самое можно играть вдвоем
put likes on the
ставьте лайки
video to your friends to
видео своим друзьям чтобы